jatt.us 2014-05-02

# Privacy Policy | JATT.US - Punjabi Videos | Punjabi Film Downloads | Punjabi Music Download

Privacy Policy for www.jatt.us  
The privacy of our visitors to www.jatt.us is important to us.

At www.jatt.us, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit www.jatt.us, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.jatt.us to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

* * *

**Contact Us  
**

, 

* * *

  * %swww jatt
  * r v feat joban sandhu song adawaa
  * pajabi video song hd download
  * djpunjbcomvido
  * honey singh blue eyes video9
  * PrivacyPolicy|JATT US-PunjabiVideos|PunjabiFilmDownloads|PunjabiMusicDownload
  * Video9 in punjabi song kudi Tu pataka
  * Video9 in punjb
  * Adawa rv feat joban sidhu
  * jatt airways new pajabi movie video song down
  * aaibo gudi teri song download
  * Miss pooja video9 song download com
  * pooja video9com song downloading
  * pooja punjabi video9
  * kudi tu patkha song video9
  * miss pooja in video9 com
  * pajabi song miss pooja video 9
  * newjatt pajabi
  * newjatt com@Rd panjabi
  * Newjatt com miss pooja pun film mp3 songs
  * miss pooja video9
  * new punjabi song harpreet dhillondj punjb com
  * Miss pooja video9 in
  * new punjbi movie song dwonload video9 in
  * misspoojavideo9 com
  * New punjabi mp3 song adawa by joban sandhu
  * punjab video songs download video9 com
  * www video9 miss poja com
  * www punjabi mp3 song adawa com
  * www new jatt com popups
